Put your hand on your chest
Can you feel it?
Thump, Thump, Thump
That's the sound of me working hard. Pumping blood all around your body
Oh my Goodness! What? Who are you?
Hi! I'm ECG
My job is to help doctors make sure you stay healthy
Really? How?
By placing these little cameras on your body
Don't worry
They don't hurt at all
What do these cameras do?
When you're pumping blood and moving around
They help me see your movements
And draw pictures of them
Just Remember
Before the test, your skin should be clean
And you shouldn't put any lotion or oil on it
Alright, ECG
Great! Now, While I attach the cameras
Try not to talk
And stay as still as you can
That's so cool!
I can see my own heartbeat right here
See these lines?
They show what a healthy heart looks like
Wow! I'm gonna play, exercise and eat lots of healthy foods to stay strong
Thanks, ECG
Now I know so much more about myself
From now on, I'll take even better care